<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Switch games on Metacritic</title><link>https://metacritic.com/</link><description>Switch games on Metacritic</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>https://external-content.duckduckgo.com/iu/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fupload.wikimedia.org%2Fwikipedia%2Fcommons%2Fthumb%2F2%2F20%2FMetacritic.svg%2F1024px-Metacritic.svg.png&amp;f=1&amp;nofb=1</url><title>Switch games on Metacritic</title><link>https://metacritic.com/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 12:53:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Shin Megami Tensei V</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/shin-megami-tensei-v/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/8/37239c2b17a0c372da61df17e4fb3e9f-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ambitions of god and human clash amidst the horror of a dying world. Neither human nor demon, the newly-forged Nahobino and his friends must decide what is worth saving... and prepare to sacrifice everything in its name. In a world without its Creator, which path will you choose?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;12 November 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;86&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">6036303e9b77bb384ae51e64692da42d</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/8/37239c2b17a0c372da61df17e4fb3e9f-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Unpacking</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/unpacking/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/2/8254e9fe67a7baaadea41ebfe77dba62-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unpacking is a zen puzzle game about the familiar experience of pulling possessions out of boxes and fitting them into a new home. Part block-fitting puzzle, part home decoration, you are invited to create a satisfying living space while learning clues about the life you’re unpacking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;02 November 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;82&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">3199934a5ad47e7c8b04e68f1b2cd983</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/2/8254e9fe67a7baaadea41ebfe77dba62-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>The Caligula Effect 2</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/the-caligula-effect-2/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/3/4910608e68d4abc130f0fbfe4d302e08-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dive into a reality-warping adventure from Persona scenario-writer Tadashi Satomi and director Takuya Yamanaka!

A virtuadoll named Regret has created the world of Redo in order to save people from their past regrets by unknowingly imprisoning them in a simulation. However, this "Paradise" is shaken to the core when a virtual idol named X breaks into Regret's virtual reality and restores a high school student's memories of the real world. In order to escape Redo, they form the Go-Home Club, a resistance group that seeks to fight against regret and her enforcers, the Obbligato Musicians.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;19 October 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;84&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">fa0b2344158c658e1d5adc4af7e5a5ee</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/3/4910608e68d4abc130f0fbfe4d302e08-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Disco Elysium: The Final Cut</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/disco-elysium-the-final-cut/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/0/b6b93780ed1e4e0440a5e990f0ce1432-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disco Elysium - The Final Cut is the definitive edition of the smash-hit RPG. Pursue your political dreams in new quests, meet and question more of the city's locals, and explore a whole extra area. Full voice-acting, controller support, and expanded language options also included.

Get even more out of this award-winning open world. You're a detective with a unique skill system at your disposal and a whole city block to carve your path across. Interrogate unforgettable characters, crack murders, or take bribes. Become a hero or an absolute disaster of a human being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;12 October 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;86&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">96c8699d7056f372f37d439745650f32</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/0/b6b93780ed1e4e0440a5e990f0ce1432-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Metroid Dread</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/metroid-dread/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/5/33ebb325c3be6cf63c66ef82c2e66574-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join intergalactic bounty hunter Samus Aran in her first new 2D Metroid™ story in 19 years. Samus’ story continues after the events of the Metroid™ Fusion game when she descends upon planet ZDR to investigate a mysterious transmission sent to the Galactic Federation. The remote planet has become overrun by vicious alien lifeforms and chilling mechanical menaces. Samus is more agile and capable than ever, but can she overcome the inhuman threat stalking the depths of ZDR?&#13;
&#13;
Face off against unrelenting E.M.M.I. robots&#13;
&#13;
Once DNA-extracting research machines, the imposing E.M.M.I. are now hunting Samus down. Tensions are high as you evade these E.M.M.I. to avoid a cruel death while finding a way to take them down. Find out what turned these robotic wonders into the scourge of ZDR and escape with your life.&#13;
&#13;
Feel Samus’ power grow as you gain maneuvers and abilities&#13;
&#13;
Acquire new and familiar abilities as you traverse the many environments of this dangerous world. Parkour over obstacles, slide through tight spaces, counter enemies, and battle your way through the planet. Return to areas and use your new abilities to find upgrades, alternate paths, and a way forward. Explore the sprawling map, evade and destroy E.M.M.I. robots, and overcome the dread plaguing ZDR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;08 October 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;88&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">a746160f0345ddbae8efa68f96fc7b5d</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/5/33ebb325c3be6cf63c66ef82c2e66574-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Ni no Kuni II: Revenant Kingdom - Prince's Edition</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/ni-no-kuni-ii-revenant-kingdom---princes-edition/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/7/aec76b7280b9a04ed4b7795257d4dcaf-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ni No Kuni 2 kicks off with the President of a real-world Earth country transported to a magical kingdom in which every person is also sort of an animal as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;17 September 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;81&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">28fbc35234594cee18cf5cdf85a6d6b9</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/7/aec76b7280b9a04ed4b7795257d4dcaf-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Eastward</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/eastward/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/9/173e1f1c9224f2c82146c0c5e3e19c35-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the near-future, society is starting to collapse, and the human population is at an all-time low. A deadly toxic presence has spread across the land, destroying and devouring everything in its path.

Those who could escape the miasma flocked to underground villages to start a new life. But for a hardworking miner and a mysterious young girl, the hope of a thriving outside world beckons

Escape the tyrannical clutches of Sandfill's subterranean society and join Eastward's unlikely duo on an exciting adventure to the land above! 

Discover beautiful yet bizarre settlements and make new friends as you travel across the world by rail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;16 September 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;84&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">2e7468010bb42704668037b55586a3b3</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/9/173e1f1c9224f2c82146c0c5e3e19c35-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>The Great Ace Attorney Chronicles</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/the-great-ace-attorney-chronicles/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/5/1e8fe505538597a820f12f1ae317eb0c-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With all the fun and drama of the Ace Attorney series set against the backdrop of Victorian-era Britain and Japan, there's sure to be no "Objection!" to the adventures of Ryunosuke Naruhodo as he turns the courtroom upside down. Featuring an intriguing overarching mystery spanning across two games, it promises to be the most engrossing story in the series yet. [Capcom]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;27 July 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;87&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">22dc890b99ba0f5376c0b905d0b15a74</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/5/1e8fe505538597a820f12f1ae317eb0c-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>NEO: The World Ends With You</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/neo-the-world-ends-with-you/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/2/6f49b9b82cbad73dbe421d5426435bbe-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Only the possibility of you can change our fate". A long-awaited new story in The World Ends with You series has arrived. Rindo comes to the grim realization that his life is on the line when he is forced to compete in the so-called "Reapers' Game." There's no telling how this tale will unfold—but it's up to you to find out! Put your psychic prowess to the test as you duke it out on the stylishly animated streets of Shibuya. Features:  Delve into a vividly illustrated Shibuya, animated with style, music and monsters. Collect and wield hundreds of Psych abilities to battle surreal threats. Investigate the world around you and beat the "Reapers' Game" to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;27 July 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;83&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">a24e320b6ab4d80e8cc36587e24dba90</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/2/6f49b9b82cbad73dbe421d5426435bbe-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>The Legend of Zelda: Skyward Sword HD</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/the-legend-of-zelda-skyward-sword-hd/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/2/6d4ac4f9ecf3a6100e47e4b0436885cf-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take to the skies, draw your sword, and experience the earliest story in the Legend of Zelda series. Join Link in his high-flying quest to save Zelda, a childhood friend who must confront her destiny. Soar between floating islands and descend to the treacherous surface world in this updated HD version of the Legend of Zelda: Skyward Sword. Master realistic swordplay that matches your movements. Swing your sword and angle your slashes to uncover and break through opponents’ defenses using intuitive motion controls. Link will match the angle of each strike you make with the Joy-Con controller, creating immersive swordplay that relies on strategy and accuracy. Movements feel smoother and more immediate thanks to the Nintendo Switch system’s increased processing power and HD graphics. Take advantage of the newly-added button only control scheme—perfect for playing in handheld mode or on the Nintendo Switch Lite system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;16 July 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;81&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">37901ceddc551f343dbd00de4245a83a</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/2/6d4ac4f9ecf3a6100e47e4b0436885cf-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Monster Hunter Stories 2: Wings of Ruin</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/monster-hunter-stories-2-wings-of-ruin/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/9/92fe867164a58697eb5fe6c1fe750e42-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monster Hunter Stories 2: Wings of Ruin offers both RPG and Monster Hunter fans a unique new experience with a rich storyline featuring charming characters, challenging quests and friendly encounters with familiar monsters from the Monster Hunter series. Assuming the role of a young Monster Rider who can use a Kinship Stone to form strong bonds with monsters, players can gain experience and improve their skills to form deeper connections with these wonderful creatures. When ready, players can embark on memorable adventures filled with dramatic events and heartwarming friendships as the epic tale unfolds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;09 July 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;81&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">67ee29513fbe5a62f714b87a1ceefa29</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/9/92fe867164a58697eb5fe6c1fe750e42-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 1 + 2</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/tony-hawks-pro-skater-1-+-2/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/4/a12de24a39ac3fd6869111a9bdb7c92e-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drop back in with the most iconic skateboarding games ever made. Play Tony Hawk's Pro Skater &amp; Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 in one epic collection, rebuilt from the ground up in incredible HD. All the pro skaters, levels and tricks are back and fully-remastered, plus more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;25 June 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;84&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">e336f6ccee62b54b431d9412b374a520</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/4/a12de24a39ac3fd6869111a9bdb7c92e-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>The Legend of Heroes: Trails of Cold Steel IV</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/the-legend-of-heroes-trails-of-cold-steel-iv/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/3/b8744c66ef9b466177f062cabb7bac15-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Erebonian Empire is on the brink of all out war! Taking place shortly after the ending of Trails of Cold Steel III, the heroes of Class VII find themselves against the full force of the Empire in an attempt to stop its path of total domination. Further, the hero of the Erebonian Civil War and Class VII's instructor, Rean Schwarzer, has gone missing. Now, the students of Class VII, old and new, must unite with heroes from all over the continent to create the only chance the world has to be spared from total destruction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;09 April 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;82&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">a5c07c71c8300b138b5e9665dde5d594</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/3/b8744c66ef9b466177f062cabb7bac15-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Monster Hunter Rise</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/monster-hunter-rise/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/8/64c56e042957be2a3f8a2b66d7311ab0-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rise to the challenge and join the hunt. The action-RPG series returns to the Nintendo Switch! Set in the ninja-inspired land of Kamura Village, explore lush ecosystems and battle fearsome monsters to become the ultimate hunter. It's been half a century since the last calamity struck, but a terrifying new monster has reared its head and threatens to plunge the land into chaos once again.&#13;
&#13;
Hunt solo or in a party with friends to earn rewards that you can use to craft a huge variety of weapons and armor. Brand new gameplay systems such as the high-flying 'Wire Action' and your canine companion 'Palamute' will add exciting new layers to the already robust combat that Monster Hunter is known for.&#13;
&#13;
Whether it's at home, on the go, online or offline - you'll always be ready for your next hunt on the Nintendo Switch!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;26 March 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;87&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">13fc82458d0807b3c058aa3184fb104b</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/8/64c56e042957be2a3f8a2b66d7311ab0-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Crash Bandicoot 4: It's About Time</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/switch/crash-bandicoot-4-its-about-time/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/8/a3c702cf7390447b10a7928a121f36a3-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's About Time - for a brand-wumping new Crash Bandicoot game! Crash fourward into a time shattered adventure with your favorite marsupials. Neo Cortex and N. Tropy are back at it again and launching an all-out assault on not just this universe, but the entire multiverse! Crash and Coco are here to save the day by reuniting the four Quantum Masks and bending the rules of reality. New abilities? Check. More playable characters? Yep. Alternate dimensions? Obviously. Ridonkulous bosses? For sure. Same awesome sauce? You bet your sweet jorts. Wait, are they actually jorts? Not in this universe!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;12 March 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;81&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">35279e878f15488b06aa4c7022f4e606</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/8/a3c702cf7390447b10a7928a121f36a3-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Super Mario 3D World + Bowser's Fury</title><link>https://metacritic.com//game/switch/super-mario-3d-world-+-bowsers-fury/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/5/3a4b4d7a5d852810792f55c815bb6fc3-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cat's out of the bag, Super Mario 3D World is on to the Nintendo Switch system. Pounce and climb through dozens of colorful stages! Mario (and his friends) can use power-ups like the Super Bell, which grants catlike abilities, like climbing and scratching. Work together locally or online with up to three other players to reach the goaland to see who can get a high score. The Super Mario 3D World + Bowser's Fury game features the same great co-op gameplay, creative levels and power-ups as the original game, but also so much more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;12 February 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;89&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">faa24142fd526584817bc2dd6a43cb62</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/5/3a4b4d7a5d852810792f55c815bb6fc3-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Littlewood</title><link>https://metacritic.com//game/switch/littlewood/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/0/e937603e99ac80b983af5dadc90d0558-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world has already been saved. Now it's time to rebuild your town, learn new hobbies, and forge lifelong friendships in this peaceful and relaxing RPG.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;25 February 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;86&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">3f2eb04f172d3f157189a81651a76bde</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/0/e937603e99ac80b983af5dadc90d0558-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item></channel></rss>