<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>movies on Metacritic</title><link>https://metacritic.com/</link><description>movies on Metacritic</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>https://external-content.duckduckgo.com/iu/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fupload.wikimedia.org%2Fwikipedia%2Fcommons%2Fthumb%2F2%2F20%2FMetacritic.svg%2F1024px-Metacritic.svg.png&amp;f=1&amp;nofb=1</url><title>movies on Metacritic</title><link>https://metacritic.com/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 13:53:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>In the Heights</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/in-the-heights/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/0/b7ac6a5ed5abca4e28dab0785c092bc6-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lights up on Washington Heights...The scent of a cafecito caliente hangs in the air just outside of the 181st Street subway stop, where a kaleidoscope of dreams rallies this vibrant and tight-knit community. At the intersection of it all is the likeable, magnetic bodega owner Usnavi (Anthony Ramos), who saves every penny from his daily grind as he hopes, imagines and sings about a better life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;31 August 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;84&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">90c979a65ee1d981b6146e224f718588</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/0/b7ac6a5ed5abca4e28dab0785c092bc6-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Beginning</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/beginning/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/5/5046e2a32da3e1b29c2d167520181995-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a sleepy provincial town, a Jehovah Witness community is attacked by an extremist group. In the midst of this conflict, the familiar world of Yana, the wife of the community leader, slowly crumbles. Yana's inner discontent grows as she struggles to make sense of her desires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;24 August 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;81&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">641516f3f88c9b54ae6d43214c2c5fcb</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/5/5046e2a32da3e1b29c2d167520181995-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>The Truffle Hunters</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/the-truffle-hunters/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/4/9da502d23c398a08979fe848125bb801-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deep in the forests of Piedmont, Italy, a handful of men, seventy or eighty years young, hunt for the rare and expensive white Alba truffle—which to date has resisted all of modern science's efforts at cultivation. They're guided by a secret culture and training passed down through generations, as well as by the noses of their cherished and expertly-trained dogs. They live a simpler, slower way of life, in harmony with their loyal animals and their picture-perfect land, seemingly straight out of a fairy tale. They're untethered to cell phone screens or the Internet, opting instead to make their food and drink by hand and prioritizing in-person connections and community. &#13;
The demand for white truffles increases year after year, even as the supply decreases. As a result of climate change, deforestation, and the lack of young people taking up the mantle, the truffle hunters' secrets are more coveted than ever. However, as it soon becomes clear, these ageing men may just hold something much more valuable than even this prized delicacy: the secret to a rich and meaningful life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;17 August 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;85&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">2743f5d748477b009ce440b22acc43dd</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/4/9da502d23c398a08979fe848125bb801-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Small Axe: Red, White and Blue</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/red-white-and-blue/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/6/9904dbb2efab4fa52c82438098cc18b8-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leroy Logan (John Boyega) is a young forensic scientist with a yearning to do more than his solitary laboratory work. When he sees his father assaulted by two policemen, he finds himself driven to revisiting a childhood ambition to become a police officer; an ambition borne from the naïve hope of wanting to change racist attitudes from within.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;17 August 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;84&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">86f879ff972f77f74a4105041f42d992</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/6/9904dbb2efab4fa52c82438098cc18b8-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Small Axe: Mangrove</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/mangrove/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/3/a2cde5e42f5695a83e4355d79a1ea97b-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mangrove tells the story of a restaurant and its owner in London’s Notting Hill; repeated police harassment leads to a protest march where nine arrests are made and result in a show trial at the Old Bailey in 1971, making legal history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;17 August 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;90&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">a81b5ba87956f4ca4bd730a0976d474e</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/3/a2cde5e42f5695a83e4355d79a1ea97b-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Small Axe: Lovers Rock</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/lovers-rock/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/3/62cf544058e622ab0c3eb4056cadf454-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A single evening at a house party in 1980s West London sets the scene, developing intertwined relationships against a background of violence, romance and music.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;17 August 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;95&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">b2e183bf07275e8550b3669704474381</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/3/62cf544058e622ab0c3eb4056cadf454-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Small Axe: Education</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/education/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/5/49b20b5e676535fd48b76229c3d37bc2-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Education is the coming of age story of 12-year-old Kingsley (Kenyah Sandy), who has a fascination for astronauts and rockets. When Kingsley is pulled to the headmaster's office for being disruptive in class, he discovers he's being sent to a school for those with "special needs." Distracted by working two jobs, his parents (Sharlene Whyte, Daniel Francis) are unaware of the unofficial segregation policy at play, preventing many Black children from receiving the education they deserve, until a group of West Indian women take matters into their own hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;17 August 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;87&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">6cb417d8507c5e154c1eb3905bfef706</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/5/49b20b5e676535fd48b76229c3d37bc2-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Riders of Justice</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/riders-of-justice/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/6/9a41da7fc45eeacee50d150260278ee7-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently-deployed Markus (Mads Mikkelsen) is forced to return home to care for his teenage daughter after his wife is killed in a tragic train accident. But when a survivor of the wrecked train surfaces claiming foul play, Markus begins to suspect his wife was murdered and embarks on a revenge-fueled mission to find those responsible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;17 August 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;81&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">9fb11561d5152c83b6f4fdaf64e5548c</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/6/9a41da7fc45eeacee50d150260278ee7-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>You Will Die At Twenty</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/you-will-die-at-20/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/8/0fd39601750eb4b251855f72588a3890-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During her son’s naming ceremony, a Sheikh predicts that Sakina’s child will die at the age of 20. Haunted by this prophecy, Sakina becomes overly protective of her son Muzamil, who grows up knowing about his fate. As Muzamil escapes Sakina’s ever-watchful eye, he encounters friends, ideas and challenges that make him question his destiny.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;10 August 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;81&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">31e7b51111bece68e2d33fccf5166506</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/8/0fd39601750eb4b251855f72588a3890-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>There Is No Evil</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/there-is-no-evil/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/0/0b3b0aa082c7fbb55b328dc5a0dc6443-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shot in secret and smuggled out of Iran, There is No Evil is an anthology film comprising four moral tales about men faced with a simple yet unthinkable choice – to follow orders to enforce the death penalty, or resist and risk everything. Whatever they decide, it will directly or indirectly affect their lives, their relationships, and their consciences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;13 July 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;83&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">998e37fb5cb4484a6da38eb3f173a7e3</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/0/0b3b0aa082c7fbb55b328dc5a0dc6443-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Rose Plays Julie</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/rose-plays-julie/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/0/856aac4fe5aae88f12083d560a3dd5da-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rose (Ann Skelly) is at university studying veterinary science. An only child, she has enjoyed a loving relationship with her adoptive parents. However, for as long as Rose can remember she has wanted to know who her biological parents are and the facts of her true identity. After years trying to trace her birth mother, Rose now has a name and a number. All she has to do is pick up the phone and call. When she does it quickly becomes clear that her birth mother has no wish to have any contact. Rose is shattered. A renewed and deepened sense of rejection compels her to keep going. Rose travels from Dublin to London in an effort to confront her birth mother, Ellen (Orla Brady).  Ellen is deeply disturbed when Rose turns up unannounced. The very existence of this young woman threatens the stability of the new life Ellen has painstakingly put together. But Rose proves very tenacious and Ellen is forced to reveal a secret she has kept hidden for over 20 years. This shocking revelation forces Rose to accept the violent nature of how she came into existence.  Rose believes she has little to lose but much to gain when she sets out to confront her biological father, Peter (Aidan Gillen). What Rose cannot possibly foresee is that she is on a collision course that will prove both violent and unsettling – dark forces gather and threaten to destroy her already fragile sense of her own identity. [Film Movement]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;13 July 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;86&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">a5c9cc2772af6d98fbba7c82d14aa9d6</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/0/856aac4fe5aae88f12083d560a3dd5da-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Street Gang: How We Got to Sesame Street</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/street-gang-how-we-got-to-sesame-street/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/7/f370606b93439859b9ff7cb4a6f18bcb-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take a stroll down Sesame Street and witness the birth of the most impactful children's series in TV history. From the iconic furry characters to the classic songs you know by heart, learn how a gang of visionary creators changed our world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;06 July 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;82&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">8b1467457d86ab3f8c4b808a4788b74d</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/7/f370606b93439859b9ff7cb4a6f18bcb-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>To the Ends of the Earth</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/to-the-ends-of-the-earth/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/8/f6d07c0aa395e20ac5857768a4151b57-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yoko (Atsuko Maeda) travels with a small crew to Uzbekistan to shoot an episode of her travel reality show. In front of the camera, her persona is carefree and happy-go-lucky, but behind the scenes she is cautious and introverted. Despite her best efforts, the filming of the television series ends unsuccessfully, and frustrated by the failure, she sets off into the mysterious country. Lost in the streets of Tashkent, she finds herself adrift and alone, confronting her deepest fears and hidden aspirations. [KimStim]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;08 June 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;85&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">8d852cf7c413c243150dab3d840c0b1d</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/8/f6d07c0aa395e20ac5857768a4151b57-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Stray</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/stray-2021/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/7/e53b5c65a979bb86df38e4b2a7476668-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stray explores what it means to live as a being without status or security, following three strays as they embark on inconspicuous journeys through Turkish society. Zeytin, fiercely independent, embarks on adventures through the city at night; Nazar, nurturing and protective, easily befriends the humans around her; while Kartal, a shy puppy living on the outskirts of a construction site, finds companions in the security guards who care for her. The strays’ disparate lives intersect when they each form intimate bonds with a group of young Syrians with whom they share the streets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;01 June 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;83&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">9508a1e667c7b7fd1e9dddfdb1ab7c4e</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/7/e53b5c65a979bb86df38e4b2a7476668-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Wojnarowicz</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/wojnarowicz/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/4/b418fe45aecf8fe3025ab4a531cd4cb2-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wojnarowicz: F**k You F*ggot F**ker is a fiery and urgent documentary portrait of downtown New York City artist, writer, photographer, and activist David Wojnarowicz. As New York City became the epicenter of the AIDS epidemic in the 1980s, Wojnarowicz weaponized his work and waged war against the establishment’s indifference to the plague until his death from it in 1992 at the age of 37. Exclusive access to his breathtaking body of work – including paintings, journals, and films – reveals how Wojnarowicz emptied his life into his art and activism. Rediscovered answering machine tape recordings and intimate recollections from Fran Lebowitz, Gracie Mansion, Peter Hujar, and other friends and family help present a stirring portrait of this fiercely political, unapologetically queer artist. [Kino Lorber]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;18 May 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;90&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">e2114ff266be3d37b47e61705209b9ff</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/4/b418fe45aecf8fe3025ab4a531cd4cb2-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Minari</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/minari/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/1/327485568f05d8580f76e631154b7f8b-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A tender and sweeping story about what roots us, Minari follows a Korean-American family that moves to a tiny Arkansas farm in search of their own American Dream. The family home changes completely with the arrival of their sly, foul-mouthed, but incredibly loving grandmother. Amidst the instability and challenges of this new life in the rugged Ozarks, Minari shows the undeniable resilience of family and what really makes a home. [A24]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;18 May 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;89&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">9c31684027adaee86c42e7336990c887</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/1/327485568f05d8580f76e631154b7f8b-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>The Father</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/the-father/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/2/46b8d1ebfc48582cc54f0dbe69894d0d-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anthony is 80, mischievous, living defiantly alone and rejecting the carers that his daughter, Anne, encouragingly introduces. Yet help is also becoming a necessity for Anne; she can’t make daily visits anymore and Anthony's grip on reality is unravelling. As we experience the ebb and flow of his memory, how much of his own identity and past can Anthony cling to? How does Anne cope as she grieves the loss of her father, while he still lives and breathes before her?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;18 May 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;88&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">8f819c3467d3f9d926b7a851a92f7c3a</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/2/46b8d1ebfc48582cc54f0dbe69894d0d-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>The Reason I Jump</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/the-reason-i-jump/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/3/cb830e2f2c6532470c348d188db80cc9-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on the best-selling book by Naoki Higashida, The Reason I Jump is an immersive cinematic exploration of neurodiversity through the experiences of nonspeaking autistic people from around the world. The film blends Higashida's revelatory insights into autism, written when he was just 13, with intimate portraits of five remarkable young people. It opens a window for audiences into an intense and overwhelming, but often joyful, sensory universe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;11 May 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;83&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">61c78a26f05fc0a07605236bf11ae3db</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/3/cb830e2f2c6532470c348d188db80cc9-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Judas and the Black Messiah</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/judas-and-the-black-messiah/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/9/b95c84d2a2f9832a98c0d17dd2a8825d-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FBI informant William O’Neal (LaKeith Stanfield) infiltrates the Illinois Black Panther Party and is tasked with keeping tabs on their charismatic leader, Chairman Fred Hampton (Daniel Kaluuya). A career thief, O’Neal revels in the danger of manipulating both his comrades and his handler, Special Agent Roy Mitchell (Jesse Plemons). Hampton’s political prowess grows just as he’s falling in love with fellow revolutionary Deborah Johnson (Dominique Fishback). Meanwhile, a battle wages for O’Neal’s soul. Will he align with the forces of good? Or subdue Hampton and The Panthers by any means, as FBI Director J. Edgar Hoover (Martin Sheen) commands?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;04 May 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;85&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">d7f57684d086d49918b43f74ebf6bf07</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/9/b95c84d2a2f9832a98c0d17dd2a8825d-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Test Pattern</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/test-pattern/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/2/748c62468f8dbcb9036621783dbc9adb-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Test Pattern follows an interracial couple whose relationship is put to the test after a Black woman is sexually assaulted and her white boyfriend drives her from hospital to hospital in search of a rape kit. Their story reveals the systemic injustices and social conditioning women face when navigating sex and consent within the American patriarchy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;20 April 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;81&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">7bacd077509624ffdb085eec2a768dc6</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/2/748c62468f8dbcb9036621783dbc9adb-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Acasă, My Home</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/acas-my-home/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/8/7fdb35bd838197aae99d3dda82313bb9-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the wilderness of the Bucharest Delta, an abandoned water reservoir just outside the bustling metropolis, the Enache family lived in perfect harmony with nature for two decades, sleeping in a hut on the lakeshore, catching fish barehanded, and following the rhythm of the seasons. When this area is transformed into a public national park, they are forced to leave behind their unconventional life and move to the city, where fishing rods are replaced by smartphones and idle afternoons are now spent in classrooms. As the family struggles to conform to modern civilization and maintain their connection to each other and themselves, they each begin to question their place in the world and what their future might be. With their roots in the wilderness, the nine children and their parents struggle to find a way to keep their family united in the concrete jungle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;06 April 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;82&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">cff8e6cb4cbbf9480ec73a0e8bc21b09</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/8/7fdb35bd838197aae99d3dda82313bb9-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Soul</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/soul/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/1/95fdd79c295870cb2757fdee55bc5078-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joe Gardner is a middle-school band teacher who gets the chance of a lifetime to play at the best jazz club in town. But one small misstep takes him from the streets of New York City to The Great Before – a fantastical place where new souls get their personalities, quirks and interests before they go to Earth. Determined to return to his life, Joe teams up with a precocious soul, 22, who has never understood the appeal of the human experience. As Joe desperately tries to show 22 what’s great about living, he may just discover the answers to some of life’s most important questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;23 March 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;83&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">17bf374f6c52efc23ae6656fab1404f8</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/1/95fdd79c295870cb2757fdee55bc5078-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>On-Gaku: Our Sound</title><link>https://metacritic.com/movie/on-gaku-our-sound/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/1/eb7f5a08eacd9cf003499fbb262a416e-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you’re a bored teenager looking for thrills, sometimes the only thing you can turn to is rock ‘n roll. Having no skill, money, or even a full set of drums, a feared trio of high school delinquents nevertheless decide they are destined for musical glory in a quest to impress their only friend Aya, avoid a rival gang, and – most importantly – jam out. [GKIDS]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;09 March 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;86&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">fa8d2aaec482876a71bfdf7364c91818</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/1/eb7f5a08eacd9cf003499fbb262a416e-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>The Irishman</title><link>https://metacritic.com//movie/the-irishman/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/9/c4f0ff0f354fdbfa6411a77d60d0203e-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Irishman is an epic saga of organized crime in post-war America told through the eyes of World War II veteran Frank Sheeran (Robert De Niro), a hustler and hitman who worked alongside some of the most notorious figures of the 20th Century. Spanning decades, the film chronicles one of the greatest unsolved mysteries in American history, the disappearance of legendary union boss Jimmy Hoffa, and offers a monumental journey through the hidden corridors of organized crime: its inner workings, rivalries and connections to mainstream politics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;24 November 2020&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;94&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">f4fb55a3aa1ff29993d639fde7451ed4</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/9/c4f0ff0f354fdbfa6411a77d60d0203e-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Rolling Thunder Revue: A Bob Dylan Story by Martin Scorsese</title><link>https://metacritic.com//movie/rolling-thunder-revue-a-bob-dylan-story-by-martin-scorsese/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/5/5520ce3f52ce0b1897addfb4f4cdcba4-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rolling Thunder Revue: A Bob Dylan Story by Martin Scorsese captures the troubled spirit of America in 1975 and the joyous music that Dylan performed during the fall of that year. Part documentary, part concert film, part fever dream, Rolling Thunder is a one of a kind experience, from master filmmaker Martin Scorsese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;19 January 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;86&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">08bbf161831d9dfb2d58def09f22f48f</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/5/5520ce3f52ce0b1897addfb4f4cdcba4-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>The Climb</title><link>https://metacritic.com//movie/the-climb/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/0/e09b022541fc5c097117c347585aa78b-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kyle and Mike are best friends who share a close bond — until Mike sleeps with Kyle's fiancée. The Climb is about a tumultuous but enduring relationship between two men across many years of laughter, heartbreak and rage. It is also the story of real-life best friends who turn their profound connection into a rich, humane and frequently uproarious film about the boundaries (or lack thereof) in all close friendships.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;19 January 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;82&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">25a00152c6da58e98bd3797dfb05fa03</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/0/e09b022541fc5c097117c347585aa78b-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>The Go-Go's</title><link>https://metacritic.com//movie/the-go-gos/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/7/6b7a31c8bf62f882d4dbe6d6894417a5-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Go-Go's are the most successful female rock band of all time. This documentary chronicles the meteoric rise of a band born of the LA punk scene that not only captured but created a zeitgeist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;05 February 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;81&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">75e8acb8d9d51528b1e2b00bf5ba27ea</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/7/6b7a31c8bf62f882d4dbe6d6894417a5-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>17 Blocks</title><link>https://metacritic.com//movie/17-blocks/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/9/2e45aa33c77fe9389e4b9245b45474f4-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Footage from two decades of intimate home video is used to tell the story of the Sanford family, who live just 17 blocks from the U.S. Capitol and whose struggles with addiction and gun violence lead them through a journey of love, loss, and acceptance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;19 February 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;81&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">65a43d92842a3350817cd97aa64ff835</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/9/2e45aa33c77fe9389e4b9245b45474f4-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Collective</title><link>https://metacritic.com//movie/collective/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/4/b7d4c9083c9f7f2f52cd076238430158-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Collective follows a heroic team of journalists as they uncover shocking, widespread corruption. After a deadly nightclub fire, the mysterious death of the owner of a powerful pharmaceutical firm, and the quiet resignation of a health minister—seemingly unrelated events, all within weeks of each other—the team of intrepid reporters exposes a much larger, much more explosive political scandal. COLLECTIVE is a fast-paced, real-time detective story about truth, accountability, and the value of an independent press in partisan times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;23 February 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;95&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">b80107d74caddfe5647de9674573c923</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/movies/4/b7d4c9083c9f7f2f52cd076238430158-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item></channel></rss>