<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>PlayStation 4 games on Metacritic</title><link>https://metacritic.com/</link><description>PlayStation 4 games on Metacritic</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>https://external-content.duckduckgo.com/iu/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fupload.wikimedia.org%2Fwikipedia%2Fcommons%2Fthumb%2F2%2F20%2FMetacritic.svg%2F1024px-Metacritic.svg.png&amp;f=1&amp;nofb=1</url><title>PlayStation 4 games on Metacritic</title><link>https://metacritic.com/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 13:53:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>F1 2021</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/playstation-4/f1-2021/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/7/0b730e9bbb560767b195278b5b92827c-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every story has a beginning in F1 2021, the official videogame of the 2021 FIA Formula One world Championship. Enjoy the stunning new features of F1 2021, including the thrilling story experience 'braking point', two-player career, and get even closer to the grid with 'real-season start'. Take your team to the top in the acclaimed ten-year 'My team' Career mode, or race head-to-head in split-screen and multiplayer. Immerse yourself in the greatest racing spectacle on the planet and race with the authentic lineup of twenty heroic drivers and ten iconic teams from the 2021 Season: 'braking point' - the thrilling new story experience, new ways to play: two-player career and 'real-season start', acclaimed 'My team', split-screen and multiplayer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;16 July 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;83&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">0717ddc1040ea4ee92073768c2a10294</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/7/0b730e9bbb560767b195278b5b92827c-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Where the Heart Leads</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/playstation-4/where-the-heart-leads/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/0/bf39bf9f444cc25bcdf7f4f85ae6fda7-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the kind of stormy night that can change a person’s destiny, an enormous sinkhole opens in the middle of Whit Anderson’s farm. Braving the rumbling thunder and the driving rain, Casey—their curious Golden Retriever—ventures too close to the gaping maw and tumbles in. Desperate to save her, Whit descends into the darkness, and emerges in a realm beyond his imagining. In this strange world, constantly shifting like the stops and starts of a dream, Whit bears witness to the story of his life and gains the power to change it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;13 July 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;81&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">3ff1830d8278ff4bc47cc866fab6bda3</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/0/bf39bf9f444cc25bcdf7f4f85ae6fda7-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Mass Effect Legendary Edition</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/playstation-4/mass-effect-legendary-edition/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/4/b7c8b6aa216f3877ffd0c36ee3e9a7a5-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For many months now, our team at BioWare has been hard at work updating the textures, shaders, models, effects and technical features of three enormous games. Our goal was not to remake or reimagine the original games, but to modernize the experience so that fans and new players can experience the original work in its best possible form. It's been amazing to see the adventures of Commander Shepard take on new life in super-sharp resolution, faster framerates, and beautiful visual enhancements. &#13;
&#13;
Mass Effect Legendary Edition includes single-player base content and DLC from Mass Effect, Mass Effect 2, and Mass Effect 3, plus promo weapons, armors, and packs - all remastered and optimized for 4k Ultra HD. It will be available in Spring 2021 for Xbox One, PlayStation 4, and PC, with forward compatibility and targeted enhancements on Xbox Series X and PlayStation 5.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;14 May 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;89&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">0edcf98e7c877bfda632f012ead3c8de</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/4/b7c8b6aa216f3877ffd0c36ee3e9a7a5-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>NieR Replicant ver.1.22474487139...</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/playstation-4/nier-replicant-ver122474487139/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/1/dcf50f448f700bf6b24529c1db04a00d-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get ready to experience where the NieR series all began - NieR Replicant ver.1.22474487139...Set in a post-apocalyptic world, NieR Replicant ver.1.22474487139 is puts you in the role of the titular Nier, a young man on a quest to cure his sister Yonah of a deadly disease. What they discover will make them question everything they thought they knew The original NieR release has an interesting history. In Japan, there were two versions of the game: NieR Replicant and NieR Gestalt. NieR Replicant focused on Brother Nier and his sister Yonah. In NieR Gestalt, the main character was Father Nier, and Yonah his daughter. Only NieR Gestalt released in the West (under the name NIER) - so excitingly, this will be the first time many people will have played the Replicant version of the game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;23 April 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;84&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">a027db0b6253d60b9813c1a0c14525c4</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/1/dcf50f448f700bf6b24529c1db04a00d-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>It Takes Two</title><link>https://metacritic.com/game/playstation-4/it-takes-two/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/3/df29d539fc01ab1dbf7b624fdf0be089-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From Hazelight comes It Takes Two an innovative co-op adventure where uniquely varied gameplay and emotional storytelling intertwine in a fantastical journey. Founded to push the creative boundaries of what's possible in games, Hazelight is the award-winning studio behind the critically acclaimed A Way Out and Brothers: A Tale of Two Sons.&#13;
&#13;
Something out of the ordinary&#13;
Bring your favorite co-op partner and together step into the shoes of May and Cody. As the couple is going through a divorce, through unknown means their minds are transported into two dolls which their daughter, Rose, made to represent them. Now they must reluctantly find a way to get back into their bodies, a quest which takes them through the most wild, unexpected and fantastical journey imaginable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;26 March 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;86&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">5fcc7311567e71079c1cbcbf20318c12</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/3/df29d539fc01ab1dbf7b624fdf0be089-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Little Nightmares II</title><link>https://metacritic.com//game/playstation-4/little-nightmares-ii/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/3/26ee07ee97a4e636fafa5a16153f1543-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Little Nightmares II is a suspense-adventure game in which you play as Mono, a young boy trapped in a world that has been distorted by a mysterious transmission from a distant signal tower. With Six, the girl in a yellow raincoat, Mono sets out to discover the dark secrets of The Signal Tower and save Six from her terrible fate; but their journey will not be easy as Mono and Six will face an array of new threats from the terrible residents of this world. Will you dare face this collection of new, little nightmares? PLAY A DARK, THRILLING, SUSPENSE ADVENTURE: A host of brand-new residents lie in wait to haunt your steps and disturb your sleep. Outsmart the sadistic teacher, survive the bloodthirsty hunter and flee from many more terrifying characters, as Mono and Six journey through this world together. DISCOVER A FANTASTICAL WORLD CORRUPTED BY THE SIGNAL TOWER: Escape a world that’s rotten from the inside. Your journey will take you from creepy woodlands to sinister schools on your way to the dreadful Signal Tower. Find the source of the evil that spreads through the TV screens of the world. AWAKEN YOUR INNER CHILD TO SAVE SIX FROM THE DARKNESS: Six is fading from this world, and her only hope is to journey with Mono to find what has afflicted her from the Signal Tower. In this world of unknown terrors, you are her only beacon of hope. Can you gather up the courage to fend off your tormenters, and work with Six to make sense of The Signal Tower?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;11 February 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;82&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">a0bc061fdbb67e7f89af0a70a5ed20a0</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/3/26ee07ee97a4e636fafa5a16153f1543-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Persona 5 Strikers</title><link>https://metacritic.com//game/playstation-4/persona-5-strikers/critic-reviews</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/1/e21ad44cbd99adbe26b64648d47304d0-98.jpg'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sequel to the international smash-hit Persona 5 (3.2 million copies world-wide) is now available as the series' first action RPG! Featuring an all-new story set up half a year after the events of P5! &#13;
&#13;
Travel Japan! &#13;
Following the events of P5, the Phantom Thieves of Hearts gather once more during their summer break to solve the mystery behind new change of heart cases that are occurring all over Japan! &#13;
&#13;
Persona 5 is now an action RPG!&#13;
The new action battle system makes hitting enemy weak points to activate a 1 More or All-Out Attack, which fans have come to love, even easier!&#13;
&#13;
You can even use Baton Pass to play as other characters!&#13;
In the newly introduced Jails, you can switch controls between characters at any time! Clear the game with style by using different characters in unique situations!&#13;
 &#13;
New character! &#13;
Who is this new mysterious girl you meet in the Shibuya of the other world? Find out as she fights alongside you as the newest member of the Phantom Thieves of Hearts!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;19 February 2021&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;84&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">103fbcfd14f63900201c0d6ab491d0f5</guid><enclosure url="https://static.metacritic.com/images/products/games/1/e21ad44cbd99adbe26b64648d47304d0-98.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/></item></channel></rss>